data = [
    {
      "question": "What or who is 'Dracula vampira'?",
      "answerA": "person",
      "answerB": "plant",
      "answerC": "animal",
      "answerD": "club",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many people live in France (2017)",
      "answerA": "43 mio",
      "answerB": "110 mio",
      "answerC": "67 mio",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the capital of Azerbaijan?",
      "answerA": "Baku",
      "answerB": "Baka",
      "answerC": "",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "This quiz is...",
      "answerA": "awesome ;)",
      "answerB": "",
      "answerC": "",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the popular video game series, what type of animal is Sonic?",
      "answerA": "Dog",
      "answerB": "Cat",
      "answerC": "Hedgehog",
      "answerD": "Mouse",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "H2O is the chemical compound for...?",
      "answerA": "Water",
      "answerB": "Gold",
      "answerC": "Uranium",
      "answerD": "Oxygen",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the ‘MI’ in ‘MI6’ stand for?",
      "answerA": "Massive Intellect",
      "answerB": "Mighty Inc.",
      "answerC": "Military Intelligence",
      "answerD": "Manchester Inc.",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which religion is Krishna a god?",
      "answerA": "Judaism",
      "answerB": "Christianity",
      "answerC": "Hinduism",
      "answerD": "Buddhism",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the capital of Indonesia?",
      "answerA": "Bali",
      "answerB": "Bandung",
      "answerC": "Surabaya",
      "answerD": "Jakarta",
      "correct": "Kuala Lumpur"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose mother complained about his swearing in the film GoodFellas?",
      "answerA": "Ray Liotta",
      "answerB": "Joe Pesci",
      "answerC": "Robert De Niro",
      "answerD": "Paul Sorvino",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Kelvin scale measure?",
      "answerA": "Height",
      "answerB": "Toughness",
      "answerC": "Temperature",
      "answerD": "Weight",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many strings does a standard guitar have?",
      "answerA": "2",
      "answerB": "12",
      "answerC": "24",
      "answerD": "6",
      "correct": "answerD"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Alice enter Wonderland?",
      "answerA": "Large Door",
      "answerB": "Tiny Door",
      "answerC": "Rabbithole",
      "answerD": "Window",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the final act at Woodstock?",
      "answerA": "Jimi Hendrix",
      "answerB": "Janis Joplin",
      "answerC": "The Who",
      "answerD": "Joe Cocker",
      "correct": "answerA"
    }
  ];
